# TISHA PARKINSON

### WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER & SEO STRATEGIST

#### CONTACT

3

208-716-7875



tish4575@gmail.com



Ashton, Idaho

#### EDUCATION

## BACHELOR OF SCIENCE WEB DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

Brigham Young University - Idaho Apr 2019

SEO AGENCY COURSE Jan 2021

#### SKILLS

#### PDF, HTML, CSS \*\*\*\*\*

On-Page SEO \*\*\*\*\*

Ahrefs, Google Analytics, GSC \*\*\*\*

Keyword Research & Analysis \*\*\*\*

Google & Facebook Ads \*\*\*\*

Microsoft Visual Studio\*\*\*\*

Microsoft Office Suite\*\*\*\*

Adobe CC, Acrobat, Illustrator,

Photoshop, and InDesign \*\*\*\*\*

Javascript, MySQL, React \*\*\*

Problem-Solving \*\*\*\*

#### SUMMARY

I am a professional web designer and developer with **six years of experience** in website design, development and SEO work. **Excellent written and verbal communication skills.** Team player with an eye for detail and **experience working remotely and independently**.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### **SEO ANALYST**

Schumacher Marketing - Remote

#### Apr 2023 - Present

• SEO audits, keyword gap analyses, backlink audits, and content creation, optimization and implementation of client websites.

#### WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER & SEO MANAGER

Hard Hat Training - Rexburg, Idaho

#### May 2018 - Present

- Maintained websites, updated design, and globalized site styling.
- SEO Manager Implemented SEO content campaign, researched and analyzed competitor keywords, organized target keywords, created 100+ content briefs, oversaw three writer's creation of website content and compliance to content briefs and implemented that content on the website.
- Implemented site audit changes including canonicalizing URLS, deleting and redirecting unhelpful pages, creating content briefs for 150+ pages that need rewritten based on Google analytics, GSC, and Ahrefs data.

#### JUNIOR FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

Himmer Web Solutions - Remote

#### Apr 2017 - Oct 2017

- Website maintenance
- Image Optimization
- CSS Troubleshooting